<changelog>
    
    <changes>
        <version>1.2</version>
        <change>Added color compatibility with iOS 13.3.</change>
        <change>Fixed a bug on iOS 13.3 where the sliders didn't get rounded.</change>
        <change>Fixed lag when using random colors.</change>
        <changes>Fixed a bug that didn't apply custom colors on the media and volume modules.</change>
        <change>Fixed a bug that made custom colors "flash" when the module expanded on iOS 13.3</change>
        <change>Fixed a bug on iOS 13.3 that made the custom colors dissapear on some modules when the media module was transitioning to compact state.</change>
    </changes>
    <changes>
            <version>1.1.2</version>
            <change>Added optional custom color for the modules!</change>
            <change>Added random colors for the modules.</change>
            <change>Added custom color alpha for the modules.</change>
            <change>Added optional brightness and audio sliders rounded</change>
            <change>Added option to set sliders corner radius</change>
            <change>Fixed a ton of bugs</change>
            <change>Fixed a bug with a nasty transition between compact and expanded for the volume slider.</change>
    </changes>
    <changes>
            <version>1.1.1</version>
            <change>Reworked preferences, better quality icon.</change>
            <change>Added custom corner radius for compact and expanded modules to configure from settings</change>
            <change>Fixed a bug that made the volume hud get rounded sometimes</change>
            <change>Fixed a bug that sometimes didn't apply the corner radius to the media module, and more that I don't remember.</change>
            <change>Added support for 0 corner radius for a pretty cool look, see screenshots for a reference photo.</change>
            <change>Added AirPlay glyph positioning settings, and to hide the AirPlay glyph</change>
    </changes>
    
	<changes>
		<version>1.1</version>
		<change>Added preferences to configure from settings</change>
		<change>Added icon</change>
		<change>Added screenshots to the depiction</change>
	</changes>

	<changes>
		<version>1.0.1</version>
		<change>Fixed a few bugs and made some animations smoother.</change>
		<change>Fixed the AirPlay glyph in the nowplaying module to be in the middle of the module on all devices.</change>
	</changes>

	<changes>
		<version>1.0</version>
		<change>Initial Release</change>
	</changes>

</changelog>
